export const QuizData = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: `Which of the following is an advantage of using JavaScript?`,
        options: [`Less server interaction`, `Immediate feedback`, `Increased interactivity`, `All of the above.`],
        answer: `All of the above.`
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: `Which of the following is the correct syntax to print a page using JavaScript?`,
        options: [`window.print();`, `browser.print();`, `navigator.print();`, `document.print();`],
        answer: `Nwindow.print();`
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: `Which built-in method returns the character at the specified index?`,
        options: [`characterAt()`, `getCharAt()`, `charAt()`, `None of the above.`],
        answer: `charAt()`
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: `Which of the following function of Number object returns a string value version of the current number in a format that may vary according to a browser's locale settings.?`,
        options: [`toExponential()`, `toFixed()`, `toLocaleString()`, `toString()`],
        answer: `toLocaleString()`
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: `Which of the following function of String object is used to find a match between a regular expression and a string, and to replace the matched substring with a new substring?`,
        options: [`concat()`, `match()`, `search()`, `replace()`],
        answer: `replace()`
    },

    {
        id: 5,
        question: `Which of the following is an advantage of using JavaScript?`,
        options: [`Less server interaction`, `Immediate feedback`, `Increased interactivity`, `All of the above.`],
        answer: `All of the above.`
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: `Which of the following is the correct syntax to print a page using JavaScript?`,
        options: [`window.print();`, `browser.print();`, `navigator.print();`, `document.print();`],
        answer: `Nwindow.print();`
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: `Which built-in method returns the character at the specified index?`,
        options: [`characterAt()`, `getCharAt()`, `charAt()`, `None of the above.`],
        answer: `charAt()`
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: `Which of the following function of Number object returns a string value version of the current number in a format that may vary according to a browser's locale settings.?`,
        options: [`toExponential()`, `toFixed()`, `toLocaleString()`, `toString()`],
        answer: `toLocaleString()`
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: `Which of the following function of String object is used to find a match between a regular expression and a string, and to replace the matched substring with a new substring?`,
        options: [`concat()`, `match()`, `search()`, `replace()`],
        answer: `replace()`
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: `Which of the following is an advantage of using JavaScript?`,
        options: [`Less server interaction`, `Immediate feedback`, `Increased interactivity`, `All of the above.`],
        answer: `All of the above.`
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: `Which of the following is the correct syntax to print a page using JavaScript?`,
        options: [`window.print();`, `browser.print();`, `navigator.print();`, `document.print();`],
        answer: `Nwindow.print();`
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: `Which built-in method returns the character at the specified index?`,
        options: [`characterAt()`, `getCharAt()`, `charAt()`, `None of the above.`],
        answer: `charAt()`
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: `Which of the following function of Number object returns a string value version of the current number in a format that may vary according to a browser's locale settings.?`,
        options: [`toExponential()`, `toFixed()`, `toLocaleString()`, `toString()`],
        answer: `toLocaleString()`
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: `Which of the following function of String object is used to find a match between a regular expression and a string, and to replace the matched substring with a new substring?`,
        options: [`concat()`, `match()`, `search()`, `replace()`],
        answer: `replace()`
    },
]